[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
[ENGINE WHIRRING]
♪ YO, YO ♪
♪ DROP YOUR GLASSES ♪
♪ SHAKE YOUR ASSES ♪
♪ FACE SCREWED UP LIKE
YOU HAVING HOT FLASHES ♪
♪ WHICH ONE, PICK ONE ♪
♪ THIS ONE, CLASSIC ♪
♪ RED FROM BLONDE, YEAH ♪
♪ BITCH I'M DRASTIC ♪
♪ WHY THIS, WHY THAT ♪
♪ LIPS STOP ASKING ♪
♪ LISTEN TO ME BABY ♪
♪ RELAX AND START PASSING ♪
♪ EXPRESSWAY, HEAD BACK ♪
♪ WEAVING THROUGH THE TRAFFIC ♪
♪ THIS ONE STRONG ♪
♪ SHOULD BE LABELED
AS A HAZARD ♪
♪ SOME OF Y'ALL HOT ♪
♪ SIKE, I'M GASSING ♪
♪ CLOWNS I SPOT THEM ♪
♪ AND I CAN'T STOP LAUGHING ♪
♪ EASY COME, EASY GO ♪
♪ EVE GONNA BE LASTING ♪
♪ JEALOUSY, LET IT GO ♪
♪ RESULTS COULD BE TRAGIC ♪
♪ SOME OF Y'ALL
AIN'T WRITING WELL ♪
♪ TOO CONCERNED WITH FASHION ♪
♪ NONE OF YOU AIN'T GISELLE ♪
♪ CAT WALK AND IMAGINE ♪
♪ A LOT OF Y'ALL HOLLYWOOD ♪
♪ DRAMA, CASTED ♪
♪ CUT BITCH, CAMERA OFF ♪
♪ REAL, BLAST IT ♪
♪ IF I HAD TO GIVE YOU MORE ♪
♪ IT'S ONLY BEEN A YEAR ♪
♪ NOW I'VE GOT MY FOOT
THROUGH THE DOOR ♪
♪ AND I AIN'T GOING NOWHERE ♪
♪ IT TOOK A WHILE
TO GET ME HERE ♪
♪ AND I'M GONNA TAKE MY TIME ♪
♪ DON'T FIGHT THAT
GOOD IN YOUR EAR ♪
♪ NOW LET ME BLOW YOUR MIND ♪
♪ THEY WANNA BANK UP, CRANK UP ♪
♪ MAKES ME DIZZY ♪
♪ HATERS WANNA COME AFTER ME ♪
♪ YOU AIN'T A
GANGSTER, PRANKSTER ♪
♪ TOO MUCH TV ♪
♪ SNAKES IN MY PATH ♪
♪ WANNA SMILE UP AT ME ♪
♪ NOW WHY YOU
GRITTING YOUR TEETH ♪
♪ FRUSTRATION, BABY,
YOU GOTTA BREATHE ♪
♪ TAKE A LOT MORE THAN
YOU TO GET RID OF ME ♪
♪ YOU SEE I DO WHAT
THEY CAN'T DO ♪
♪ I JUST DO ME ♪
♪ AIN'T NO STRESS WHEN
IT COMES TO STAGE ♪
♪ GET WHAT YOU SEE ♪
♪ MEET ME IN THE LAB ♪
♪ PEN AND PAD, DON'T BELIEVE ♪
♪ 16'S MINE, CREATE
MY OWN LINES ♪
♪ LOVE FOR MY WORDPLAY ♪
♪ THAT'S HARD TO FIND ♪
♪ SOPHOMORE, I AIN'T SCARED ♪
♪ ONE OF A KIND ♪
♪ ALL I DO IS CONTEMPLATE
WAYS TO MAKE YOUR FANS MINE ♪
♪ EYES BLOODSHOT, STRESSING ♪
♪ CHILLS UP YOUR SPINE ♪
♪ SICK TO YOUR STOMACH ♪
♪ WISHING I WROTE YOUR RHYMES ♪
♪ IF I HAD TO GIVE YOU MORE ♪
♪ IT'S ONLY BEEN A YEAR ♪
♪ NOW I'VE GOT MY FOOT
THROUGH THE DOOR ♪
♪ AND I AIN'T GOING NOWHERE ♪
♪ IT TOOK A WHILE
TO GET ME HERE ♪
♪ AND I'M GONNA TAKE MY TIME ♪
♪ DON'T FIGHT THAT
GOOD IN YOUR EAR ♪
♪ NOW LET ME BLOW YOUR MIND ♪
♪ LET YOUR BONES CRACK ♪
♪ YOUR BACK POP, I CAN'T STOP ♪
♪ EXCITEMENT, FROM
YOUR STASH BOX ♪
♪ THUGGED OUT, I
RESPECT THE CASH ROUTE ♪
♪ GLOCKED DOWN, BLASTERS ♪
♪ SETS WHILE I MASH OUT ♪
♪ YEAH, MASH OUT, D-R-E ♪
♪ BACKTRACK, THINK BACK, E-V-E ♪
♪ DO YOU LIKE THAT? ♪
♪ EW, YOU GOT TO, I KNOW YOU ♪
♪ HAD YOU IN A TRANCE ♪
♪ FIRST GLANCE FROM
THE FLOOR TOO ♪
♪ DON'T BELIEVE I'LL SHOW YOU ♪
♪ TAKE YOU WITH ME ♪
♪ TURN YOU ON, TENSION GONE ♪
♪ GIVE YOU RELIEF ♪
♪ PUT YOUR TRUST IN A BOMB
WHEN YOU LISTEN TO ME ♪
♪ DAMN, SHE MUCH THINNER, NO ♪
♪ NOW I'M COMPLETE, UH-HUH ♪
♪ STILL STALLION, BRICK
HOUSE, PILE IT ON ♪
♪ RIDE OR DIE BITCH ♪
♪ DOUBLE R, CAME STRONG ♪
♪ BEWARE BECAUSE I CRUSH
ANYTHING I LAND ON ♪
♪ ME HERE, AIN'T NO MISTAKE ♪
♪ IT WAS PLANNED ON ♪
♪ IF I HAD TO GIVE YOU MORE ♪
♪ IT'S ONLY BEEN A YEAR ♪
♪ NOW I'VE GOT MY FOOT
THROUGH THE DOOR ♪
♪ AND I AIN'T GOING NOWHERE ♪
♪ IT TOOK A WHILE
TO GET ME HERE ♪
♪ AND I'M GONNA TAKE MY TIME ♪
♪ DON'T FIGHT THAT
GOOD IN YOUR EAR ♪
♪ NOW LET ME BLOW YOUR MIND ♪
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]